[ar: The Winking Owl]
[ti: Bloom]
[al: BLOOMING]
[by: faycloudhiruka]
[length: 03:50]
[id: hkbohucu]
[00:01.29]Sync Lrc by Fay Cloud Hiruka

[00:05.23]The Winking Owl - Bloom

[00:21.17]Dare ni mo makerare nai yō na tokui na koto
[00:25.73]kanpeki na sōbi de idon da kedo
[00:29.42]Oh my
[00:30.92]tachihadakaru shukumei ni odorasare te
[00:35.67]shiai tochū ni ritaia

[00:40.85]yumemitsuzukeru koto wa mō tome te
[00:45.73]otonashiku hitonami de iru yo

[00:51.17]Reality knocks me down
[00:52.92]At times losing control inside .
[00:56.23]So I slow down then swim out to find what I want .
[01:01.04]Gravity makes me drown
[01:02.71]At times struggles make me stronger .
[01:06.23]Although they try to stop me
[01:08.92]My life is constantly?

[01:11.23]dare ni mo kizukare nai yō ni kotaete ta no
[01:15.98]takusan no tsukihi ga nagare ta monono
[01:19.55]Oh dear
[01:20.98]tatta hitotsu no negai sae kanae rare zu
[01:26.11]kono saki wa dō naru n da ?

[01:31.04]itami no aji o mairudo ni shi te
[01:35.67]waza kime ni denaoshi te kuru yo

[01:41.36]Reality knocks me down
[01:43.17]At times losing control inside .
[01:46.44]So I slow down then swim out to find what I want .
[01:51.11]Gravity makes me drown
[01:53.11]At times struggles make me stronger .
[01:56.55]Although they try to stop me
[01:59.05]My life is constantly blooming .
[02:08.11]
[02:21.11]omoidōri ni suru bun dake
[02:24.98]kitai no mizukasa dake ga fue te ku
[02:30.86]omoidōri ni nara nai toki
[02:34.67]kashin ni nomikomare nai yō ni

[02:40.29]Reality knocks me down
[02:42.98]At times losing control inside .
[02:45.17]So I slow down then swim out to find what I want .
[02:50.17]Gravity makes me drown
[02:51.86]At times struggles make me stronger .
[02:55.55]Although they try to stop me
[02:57.86]My life is constantly blooming .

[03:00.04]Reality knocks me down
[03:01.57]At times losing control inside .
[03:04.76]So I slow down then swim out to find what I want .
[03:09.57]Gravity makes me drown
[03:11.44]At times struggles make me stronger .
[03:14.94]Although they try to stop me
[03:17.38]My life is constantly blooming .

[03:23.45]My life is constantly blooming .

[03:29.69]Thx